groopdealz.com 2015-12-07

# GroopDealz | Today's Boutique Daily Deal

GroopDealz respects your privacy, and recognizes your concern for the way your personal information is handled and shared. We want to ensure that you are aware of our practices and know how to contact us if you have a concern. Please review our privacy policy below and note that we may occasionally update it to reflect new technologies or company procedures. 

## What Information Does GroopDealz Collect?

GroopDealz collects certain personal Information as you shop for deals or participate in other website services. We may collect your name, mailing address, telephone number, and e-mail address. We may also collect personal preferences regarding the type of deals you are interested in, businesses where you prefer to shop, or other information about your shopping preferences and patterns. Most of this information is only collected if you register as a GroopDealz member; some of this information is optional - you don't have to provide it unless you choose to, but you can still participate in GroopDealz and purchase deals. In order to make a purchase from GroopDealz, we will also collect credit card or similar financial information to complete your purchase. 

GroopDealz may collect technical information to improve its website operation. This may include your internet protocol address or information about the browser that you are using. We may also use technical tools to facilitate statistical analysis of how our website is used. By itself, this technical information does not identify you individually. 

We may use cookies to help you move more efficiently through our website. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on your computer when you visit our site. It does not identify you personally, but only tracks the settings, preferences, pages, or features associated with a particular Web site. When you return to our site, the cookie lets your browser notify our site in order to customize your visit. 

Because GroopDealz relies on credit cards for payment, we do not expect anyone under age 18 to use this website. 

## How Does GroopDealz Use Your Information?

We may use information that we collect about you to (A) to verify your identity when accessing GroopDealz; (B) to process payment for purchases that you make on GroopDealz; (C) to inform you about products, services, activities, and other subjects that we believe would be of interest; and (D) to inform our business partners regarding who has purchased deals for that business. 

We do not sell or rent your personal information to any third party, but we do provide your information to our business partners (those that provide deals on GroopDealz) as part of our agreements with them to obtain discounted products and services for GroopDealz customers. We also provide your payment information to third party payment processing companies (such as credit card processors). The privacy policies of these third parties will govern the use of your personal information after such transfers. 

If your information has changed, or if you want to correct or remove information that we maintain about you, please contact us at the address shown on the GroopDealz website. 

We rely on standard industry practices to protect the security and confidentiality of your personal information, including your credit card or other payment information. These industry practices may include encryption and secure internet protocols. We do not guarantee that your information will not be lost or misused, but we make a sincere effort to ensure that it remains secure and confidential. 

## Feedback

We welcome your feedback concerning this Privacy Policy. Please contact us at [support@groopdealz.com](mailto:support@groopdealz.com).
